{
    "subject": "Abdullah_I_of_Jordan",
    "predicate": "isMarriedTo",
    "object": "Musbah_bint_Nasser",
    "human_readable": "Abdullah I of Jordan is married to Musbah bint Nasser.",
    "questions": [
        {
            "score": 0.9442976713180542,
            "question": "Who is married to Abdullah I of Jordan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.9261323809623718,
            "question": "To whom is Musbah bint Nasser married?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.809474527835846,
            "question": "What is the name of Abdullah I of Jordan's spouse?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.788517951965332,
            "question": "Is Abdullah I of Jordan in a relationship?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7386385798454285,
            "question": "What can you tell me about the marriage of Abdullah I of Jordan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7358612418174744,
            "question": "Is Musbah bint Nasser the queen of Jordan?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.7273032665252686,
            "question": "Who is Musbah bint Nasser?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.5292909741401672,
            "question": "Can you provide more information about Abdullah I of Jordan's family?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1307317316532135,
            "question": "What is the significance of this marriage?"
        },
        {
            "score": 0.1252334713935852,
            "question": "Are there any historical events associated with this marriage?"
        }
    ],
    "google_pages": [
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Abdullah I of Jordan is married to Musbah bint Nasser.",
            "html": "yago_23184_0.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=What is the significance of this marriage?",
            "html": "yago_23184_1.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Can you provide more information about Abdullah I of Jordan's family?",
            "html": "yago_23184_2.html"
        },
        {
            "url": "https://www.google.com/search?q=Who is Musbah bint Nasser?",
            "html": "yago_23184_3.html"
        }
    ],
    "selected_docs": [
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23184_1.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23184_100.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23184_104.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23184_12.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23184_122.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23184_29.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23184_32.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23184_41.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23184_45.txt"
        },
        {
            "file_id": "yago_23184_73.txt"
        }
    ],
    "final_question": "Is true?",
    "responses": {
        "gemma2": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{'output': 'yes'}\n``` \n\n\nLet me know if you'd like to test more triples!  \n"
        },
        "llama3.1": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "Here is the evaluation:\n\n```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe information in the documents supports the triple. There are multiple mentions of Musbah bint Nasser as the first wife of Abdullah I, and it is mentioned that she became Queen Musbah of Jordan when he was proclaimed King of Jordan in 1949."
        },
        "qwen2.5": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": "```json\n{\n  \"output\": \"yes\"\n}\n```\n\nThe documents provide information that supports the statement \"Abdullah I of Jordan is married to Musbah bint Nasser.\" Multiple sources indicate that Abdullah I of Jordan married Musbah bint Nasser in 1904, and she held the title of Queen Consort when he became King of Jordan in 1949."
        },
        "mistral": {
            "short_ans": 1,
            "full_ans": " {\"output\": \"yes\"}"
        }
    },
    "need_tiebreaker": false,
    "tiebreakers_responses": {
        "mistral-nemo": {},
        "llama3.1:70b": {}
    },
    "final_decision": 1,
    "actual_decision": 1,
    "analysis": {
        "stratum": "-",
        "topic": "-"
    },
    "errors": {}
}